{
    "subject": "resource/Gustaf_VI_Adolf_of_Sweden",
    "predicate": "ontology/restingPlace",
    "object": "resource/Solna_Municipality",
    "human_readable": "The resting place of Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden is Solna Municipality.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8585766553878784,
            "question": "Is Solna Municipality in Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8000856041908264,
            "question": "In what municipality does Gustaf VI Adolf's resting place lie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.763275682926178,
            "question": "What is the name of the place where Gustaf VI Adolf is laid to rest?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.746040403842926,
            "question": "Can you tell me the resting place of Gustaf VI Adolf?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5937500596046448,
            "question": "What is the final resting place of King Gustaf VI Adolf?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5779165029525757,
            "question": "To which municipality does Solna belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5197888612747192,
            "question": "Where can you find the grave of Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48682472109794617,
            "question": "Where was Gustaf VI Adolf laid to rest after his death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4724922180175781,
            "question": "Where is Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden buried?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2993999719619751,
            "question": "If you wanted to visit the grave of Gustaf VI Adolf, where would you go?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The resting place of Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden is Solna Municipality.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5478_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden buried?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5478_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Gustaf VI Adolf laid to rest after his death?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5478_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you find the grave of Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5478_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5478_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\nLet me explain why:\n\nThe provided text states that Gustaf VI Adolf was buried in Riddarholm Church in Stockholm.  Solna Municipality is a different location.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents, Gustaf VI Adolf was buried at Riddarholm Church in Stockholm, which is located on Riddarholmen, along with other Swedish kings from Gustav II Adolf to Gustaf V. There is no mention of Solna Municipality as his resting place."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention Riddarholm Church as the burial place for many Swedish rulers, including references to King Gustaf VI Adolf's involvement in archaeological activities and his titles but do not specify that he is buried in Solna Municipality."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden was buried at Riddarholm Church, Stockholm.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "It states he was buried in Solna Municipality but text mentions Riddarholm Church which serves as the burial place of Swedish kings and  almost all Swedish rulers from Gustav II Adolf to Gustaf V are buried there.",
            "category": 0
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Gustaf VI Adolf of Sweden is actually buried at Riddarholm Church in Stockholm, not Solna Municipality.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Gustaf VI Adolf is buried at Riddarholm Church in Stockholm, not in Solna Municipality.",
            "category": 0
        }
    }
}